Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Subject Files, 2475
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files, 3101
    - Aarhus Visit – Power point presentation (CD attached – move to AV collection), 2007 October; 2479 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - ABET – Bugliarello Bio, 2008 February; 2480 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Accademia Nazionale Delle Scienze Detta Del XL, 2005 March; 2504 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - NYC Accelerator for Clean and Renewable Economy (ACRE) – Technical Advisory Board, 2009 December - 2010 February; 2481 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Achievement Rewards for College Scientists (ARCS), 1975 December - 1991 Setpember; 2497 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Advanced Research Projects Agency – Rick Lazio, 1994 February; 2498 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Air Force, 1996 June; 2483 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jeanette Albert, 2001 April - 2002 October; 2485 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Zhores I. Alferov, 1994 December; 2486 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Dr. Donald M. Alstadt, 1994 July - 1996 November, 2008 November; 2487 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Trip – Greece, 1999 May; 2489 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Trip – Turkey, 1997 December - 1998 May; 2488 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - American Institute for Medical and Biological Engineering (AIMBE), 1992 November; 2482 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - American Scientist Editorials, 1992-1993; 2490 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) - Annual Meeting, October 19, 2006, 2006 July-December; 2500 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) - Annual Meeting, October 19, 2006 – Megacities Power point presentation, 2006 September; 2501 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers (ASCE) - Annual Conference – International Program – November 5-6, 2008, 2008 March-November; 2502 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Andrew Revkin – The New York Times – Urban Sustainability, 2007 July-August; 2491 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Andy Kalotay, 2007 January; 2492 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - ANSER, 1991 November - 1994 October; 2493 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Anthony B. Giordano, 1993 August; 2494 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Argentina – October 17-20, 2010, 2010 May-October; 5390 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Argentina – October 17-20, 2010, 2010 October – 2011 September; 5391 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Artificial Intelligence Center, 1983 November - 1985 December; 2499 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Arthur Martinez, 1994 February; 2496 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Dr. Maxim S. Arzhakov, 1994 May-August; 2495 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Association For a Better New York, 1991 November; 2503 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Association of Independent Technological Universities (AITM), 1993 August; 2484 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks (AURP) - Annual Conference, May 13, 1994, 1994 December, May; 2506 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks (AURP) – Annual Conference, June 25-28, 1997, 1997 March-June; 2507 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Association of University Related Research Parks (AURP) - Career Achievement Award nominations, 2000 April - 2001 April; 2508 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Auburn University - William F. Marcuson, 2009 April –October; 2505 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Australian Local Government and Public Works Engineering Delegation visit, September 18, 2009, 2009 August - September; 2509 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - "The Automobile in America," George Bugliarello – Presentation to GM Italy-OPEL Italia Delegation, 1996 January 6; 2510 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Barbara Kates-Garnick – Urban Systems, 2007 September - 2009 March; 2518 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Bill Wulf - Honorary Degree, 2005 May - 2007 June; 2512 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Bio-design Institute at Arizona State University, 2006 November; 5392 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Bioengineering – Lecture Notes, Undated; 2513 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - "Biomedical Engineering Ethics," George Bugliarello - International Journal of Medical Implants, 2007 June - 2008 September; 2514 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Robert Bishop, 1995 February; 2515 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Erich Bloch - NSF Director, 1984 April - 1987 February; 2516 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - M. Blouke Carus – Carus Corporation, 2005 November - 2006 May; 2517 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Bob (Robert) Schiffer, 2010 May; 2511 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Bodega Project, 2004 April-May; 5393 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Bodega Project, 2006 March-May; 5394 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Bodega Project, 2007 June -2008 May; 5395 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Bodega Project – Jonathan Bowles, 2005; 5396 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Bodegas - Department of Information Technology and Telecommunications, 2003 February 5; 2519 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Centennial – "Bridge to the Future," Introduction, George Bugliarello, 1983; 2520 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Brooklyn Historical Society, 2007 January 10; 2521 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Higher Education and Bronx Economic Development Meeting, February 17, 2004, 2003 November - 2004 March; 2522 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Paolo Budinich - Trieste, 2007 April 18; 2523 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - George Bugliarello - American Academy of Water Resources Engineers (AAWRE), 2010 November; 2524 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - George Bugliarello – Activities & Achievements – Miscellaneous, 1971-1998; 2527 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - George Bugliarello - Activities & Achievements – Miscellaneous, 2000-2010, Undated; 2528 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - George Bugliarello – Bio, 1996-2010, Undated; 2529 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - George Bugliarello – Bio – Italian, 2001, 2007; 2531 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - George Bugliarello – Chancellor Activities – Miscellaneous, 1996 January - 2002 December; 2530 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - George Bugliarello - Handwritten Notes, Undated; 5397 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - George Bugliarello – Letter to Poly Community, 1994 June 27; 2532 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - George Bugliarello Scholarship, 2002 May 31; 2525 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - George Bugliarello – 1994 Tribute – Correspondence, 1994 May-August; 2533 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Spera Bugliarello (Nee Gefta-Wondrich) – Dissertation – 1924 (copy), Undated; 2526 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - New York Building Congressional Leadership – 1993 Leadership Award, 2534 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Mario Bunge – Correspondence, 1986 August - 2009 January; 2535 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Cable – Polytechnic University, 1995 December, 2008 December - 2010 December; 2536 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - John D. Calandra Italian American Institute, 2008 December 1; 2537 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Campaign for Polytechnic, 1990 August - 1994 November; 2538 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Carlo Lotti, 1996 November - 1997 March; 2539 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Carlo Messina, 1992 July - 1993 May; 2540 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Case for Polytechnic, 1997 October-November; 2541 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - "Catalyst for Change" – American Chemical Society's New York Section Symposium, 1993 October; 2551 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Center for Advanced Telecommunications Technology (CATT), 1982, 1994, 2004; 2542 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Center for Technology and the Cities – Grant Proposal Draft, Undated; 2549 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Andrew Kalotay Associates, 1994 January-June; 2584 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Brochures, Undated; 2585 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Cable article, 1995 January; 2586 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Ian Domowitz, 1993 December - 1994 March; 2588 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Inauguration, 1994 November 16; 2589 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – John F. Marshall, 1993 September - 1994 October; 2590 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Meetings, 1993 January - 1994 February; 2591 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Meeting – Notes, 1994 August 29; 2592 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Miscellaneous, 1990 December - 1994 August; 2593 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Miscellaneous, 1994 September - 1999 September, Undated; 2594 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Paul Soros, 1995 January; 2595 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Grant, 1994 April-June; 2596 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Hirsch Cohen, 1994 February-October; 2597 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Special Topics in Financial Technology Course, 1995 January-February; 2598 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - C.G. Wang – Lithium batteries, 2009 November - 2010 April; 2550 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Dato Lee Yee Chang – Correspondence, 2010 October 16; 2552 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Chemical Engineering – Sustainable Cities - Course Evaluations, 2005 February; 2543 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Chemical Engineering – Biosoma-Environmental Design of the City of the Future (CE 4053), 2008 Fall; 2544 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Chemical Engineering - New Student Orientation, 2006 May-July; 2545 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Chemical Engineering – Sustainable Cities ( CE 4043), 2003-2004; 2546 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Chemical Engineering – Department webpage, 2007 November; 2547 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 2009 February - 2010 June; 2548 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - China, 2003 November - 2004 April; 5398 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Chinese Delegation Roundtable, 2009 January-February; 2554 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Chinese Delegation Visit, 2006 September-October; 2553 (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - The Chronicle, 2002 March, 2003 April-October; 2556 (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education, 2003 April-September; 5399 (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Christopher Coccaro – Correspondence, 2009 May-June; 2555 (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Cities Transformed – Presentation, Undated; 2560 (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - City of the Future –Notes, Undated; 2559 (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Civil Engineering Department, 1996 April - 2008 October; 2562 (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Civilta del Lavoro, Undated; 2561 (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Cliff Matthews - Cosmic Beginnings / Religion of Science, 1993-1994; 2563 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Clifford Goldsmith, 1992 March - 1994 January; 2564 (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Coast Guard Academy - Saul Krasmer, 2000 November 14; 2565 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Columbia Business School speaker series, 1994 March; 2566 (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Columbia University, 2000 September-October; 5400 (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Comerint: Societa Per Azioni, 1993 April 14; 2567 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Commencement, 1991; 2568 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Commencement, 1995; 2569 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Commencement, 2010; 2570 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Commission in Higher Education, 1993 April 16; 2572 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and University (CICU), 1993 June - 1995 January; 2557 (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Commissioner of Buildings, 2005 November 1; 2571 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Human Rights, 1996 May - 2000 December; 2573 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Science Engineering & Public Policy (COSEPP) – American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1988 July-August; 2580 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Computer Network: Toward Global Intelligence, 1984 June-December; 2574 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (CIESIN), 1993 October 4; 2558 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Control of Growth as a Field of Academic Inquiry, 1974 December; 2581 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Matteo Convertino, 2010 May-June; 2575 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Cooper Union – Al Appleton, 2010 October - 2011 January; 2578 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Sean Costigan – Lower Manhattan Project, 2010 April -June; 2576 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Council for Scientific Society Presidents – "The Future of Science", 1995 December 5; 2583 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Council on Foreign Relations – New York Academy of Sciences, 1993 March - 1994 March; 2577 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "Creativity: The Hidden Dimension in Engineering and the Challenge to Engineering Education" - – American Society of Engineering Education Conference, 1987 June 21; 2582 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - CSEI Catania, 1991 June - 1996 February; 2579 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "The Culture of Government Needs to be Less Monolithic", Undated; 2599 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - CUNY, 2004 January-March; 2600 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Dias K. Daukeev, 1993 June - 1996 January; 2601 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Ruth David – Applied Systems Thinking Prize, 2008 March; 2602 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Vincent Del Gatto, 2006 December 6; 2603 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Department of Energy – Repot, 1983 August-October; 2606 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Donald Othmer – Mayor's Award of Honor for Science & Technology, 1987 February-April; 2607 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Department of State and Defense – Landmines – Laurie Freeman, 2010 May; 5402 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Dibner Chair, 2007 February 2; 2604 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Ian Domowitz – Rapporteur Summary, 1995 March-May; 2605 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Dorm Meeting, 1994 February; 2608 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Editing Notes, 2011 January; 2610 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Education Partnerships, 1989 March; 2611 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Educational Commission for Foreign Medical Graduates, 1993 August, 1994 December; 2609 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Egypt, 2008 April 18; 2613 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Giorgio Einaudi, 2005 March - 2006 February; 2614 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Fred Eirich – Obituary, 2005 May 26; 5406 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Election 2001– American Association for the Advancement of Science, 2615 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Electronic Engineering Times, 1991 January; 2616 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Elwin S. Larsen Tribute, 1991 April; 2612 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Emergency Management for Higher Education, 2008 October-December; 2617 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - "Engineering and the Future" - Correspondence, 1994 May 23; 2619 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Engineering College of Aarhus, Denmark, 2004 June 30; 5403 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Engineering Education for the 21th Century, 1987 October 10; 2618 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Engineering News-Record, 1984 November, 1992 December - 1993 February; 2620 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Engineers Forum on Sustainability, 2004 January-March; 5404 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Environmental Management Association, 2009 March; 2621 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Annual International Conference on Ethical Issues in Biomedical Engineering, 2009 April; 2622 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Evangelos Limpantoudis - RESTRICT, 2010 May 13; 2623 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Guiseppe Ferro, 2009 June 5; 2624 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Florida A&M University – Industry Day 2007, 5405 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Efi Fourfoula-Georgiou – University of Minnesota, 2008 February - 2009 January; 2625 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Future of Engineering – Notes, 1996 March 23; 2626 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - De Gao – Outstanding Graduate Award – RESTRICT, 2010 March; 2627 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Mannela Garcia, 1993 November 5; 2628 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Germany's New States, 1993 May; 2629 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Gift Acknowledgements, 1992 March-June, 1994 January-April; 2630 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Tony B. Giordano, 1992 August - 1995 October; 2631 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - William T. Golden, 2007 January; 2632 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Harvey Goldstein – Harvest International, 1992 October, 1994 February; 2633 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Thomas Graedel, 2005 February-April; 2634 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Monty Graham, 2010 May; 2635 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Richard Grasso, 1993 December; 2636 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Green Grants – Richard Wener, 2009 June; 2637 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Seymour S. Greenfield, 1992 December 10; 2639 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Greenwald Foundation, 1989 January, 2000 June; 2638 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Guest Lecture – U.S. Coast Guard Academy, 2000 November 14; 5407 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Richard E. Hanley, Journal of Urban Technology, 1994 April 29; 2641 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Morag Hann - Urban Initiative, 2006 October 17; 2642 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Garth R. Harding - "Will Megacities Survive", 2010 June; 2643 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Hemorheology & Bioengineering, Undated; 2646 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Herman F. Mark Memorial Service, 1992 April 13; 2644 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Holiday Card List, 1992; 2645 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2009 December; 2647 (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Honorary Degrees – Criteria for Candidates, 1980 November 19; 2648 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Humanity 3000 Symposium No. 1 Proceedings, 2000 August 12-16; 2649 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Tin-Kan Hung, 2007 October - 2009 July; 2650 (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Hyper Intelligence, 1984, 1990; 2651 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - IASP World Conference on Science and Technology Parks, 1997 March-June; 2652 (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - The Ideal of Civil Engineering", 1993 January 25; 2653 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Ernesto Illy, 1993 October-December; 2656 (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Indiana University – Michael Conneally, 2008 March 18; 2664 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Industrial Technology Research Institute, 1993 October; 2662 (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Infrastructure Technology & Finance, 1995 April 7; 2657 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers – Industry Relations Luncheon, 1990 December, 1991 February; 2654 (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Institute for Science, Engineering and Public Policy - Resident Scholar, 1998 May-December; 2661 (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Integrated Research for Civil Infrastructure, 1997 February; 2658 (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - International Education for Technology Management, 1992 February 20; 2659 (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - International Higher Education Academy of Sciences, 1993 December - 1994 May; 2660 (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - International Higher Education Academy of Sciences, 1997 March - 2005 June; 2655 (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Italian American Advisory Council, 1994 April 25; 2665 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Italian International Technology Fund, 1991 March 25; 2666 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Italian Scientists and Scholars of North America Foundation, 2006 December - 2008 Novemeber; 2663 (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Dr. Linda K. Jacobs, 1994 March-October; 2669 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Japan-American Frontiers of Engineering Symposium, 2010 July; 5408 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Journal of Medical Implants and Devices, 2009 June 26; 2667 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Journal of Russian Technology, Undated; 2668 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Journal of Urban Technology, 2007 January - 2009 March; 2671 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Ilan Juran – Urban Infrastructure / Sustainability Courses, 2004 September - 2007 January; 2670 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Ken Keller – Johns Hopkins School of Advanced International Studies, Bologna Center, 2006 May - 2007 January; 2673 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Robert Kelley – Media Planet, 2009 November 13; 2674 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Melissa Knothe Tate, 2010 May 3; 2675 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Korean Academy of Science & Technology, 2004 March-May, 2006 April-December; 2672 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Erich Kunhardt, 2006 August 9; 2676 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Frank Lahainer-Laniezi, 1993 December 20; 2677 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Giovanni Latorre, 2002 September; 2678 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, 2003 March - 2006 November; 2685 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Leadership Seminar Series, 1996 February-October; 2679 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Don Lebell, 2008 October - 2009 March; 2680 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Dato Lee Yee Cheong, 2010 February 5; 2681 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Liikeenjohdon Instituutti Foretagsledningsinstitutet – Finnish Institute of Management, 1992 May 18; 2683 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation – Bodega Project, 2005 September, 2006 March; 5409 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Long Island, 1993 January 27; 2686 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Long Island Lightning Company, 1994 April 13; 2684 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Long Island & Westchester Advisory Board, 1994 January; 2682 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1994 November 4; 2687 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Magazine - La Citta E La Scienza, "Un Politecnico Dal Nulla", 1999 October 24; 5434 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Gordon Mahon – Recommendation - RESTRICT, 1993 June-September; 2688 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - 2010 Marconi Prize, 2010 June; 5410 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Marconi Society, 1981-1989; 2689 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Marconi Society, 1992-1997; 2690 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Marconi Society, 2001-2006; 2691 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Marconi Society, 2007; 2692 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Marconi Society, 2008; 2693 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Marconi Society, 2009; 2694 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Marconi Society, Undated; 2695 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Master in Security Studies, 2002 August 26; 2696 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Master in Urban Sustainability – Notes, Undated; 2723 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Master of Science in Management, 1988 February 25; 2722 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Master of Technology, 1991 November; 2720 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - "Mastermind of Metrotech" – Brooklyn Progress, 1990 September; 2697 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Mayor's Advisory Council on Development & Recycling Markets, 1992 December - 1993 June; 2698 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 1994 April-December; 5414 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 1995, 1997; 5411 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 1998 July; 2699 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology – RESTRICT, 2005; 5412 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Mayor's Award of Honor for Excellence in Science and Technology - Nomination – Eli M. Pearce - RESTRICT, 1987; 5413 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 2000 August - 2001 February; 5415 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Mayor's Commission for Science & Technology, 1989 March 15; 2700 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Arthur W. Mellon Foundation – Proposal, 1981 May; 2702 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Mentoring, 2007 September-December; 2703 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Metrocities, 2005 November - 2006 May; 2704 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Mexico City – Urban Sustainability, 2008 October 2; 2705 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Henry Q. Middendorf, 1993 March 16; 2706 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - "The Middle East in 1990", William B. Quandt, 1991; 2707 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Middle States Association, 1993 February-July; 2708 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Joel Miele – Commissioner, Department of Buildings - Silk Road Project, 1994 May 9; 2710 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Mildred Topp Othmer – Memorial, 1998 July-October; 2709 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1993; 2711 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 March - 1996 February; 2712 (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous, 2004 February-March; 5417 (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous, 2006 December - 2010 October; 5416 (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous – Correspondence, 2009 April; 2713 (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous - Mailings, 2008 June-September; 2714 (Box 21, Folder 61)